{
    "questions": [
        {
            "id": "1",
            "question": "4p/(3t) - 9p/(8t). Which of the following expressions is equivalent to the expression above for t \u2260 0?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "p/(24t)",
                "-p/(24t)",
                "5p/(24t)",
                "-5p/(24t)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "-p/(24t)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtracting the two fractions results in -p/(24t).",
            "difficulty": 4
        },
        {
            "id": "2",
            "question": "5/(16z) + z/16. Which expression is equivalent to the above sum for z \u2260 0 ?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "(z^2+5)/16",
                "(z^2+5)/32",
                "(z^2-5)/32",
                "16z"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(z^2+5)/16",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Addition of the two terms results in (z^2+5)/16",
            "difficulty": 4
        },
        {
            "id": "3",
            "question": "(10q/30r+28 - 5q+12/6r+9), Which expression is equivalent to the above difference?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "(10q^2 - 28q + 12) / (30r + 18)",
                "(-18q + 12) / (30r + 18)",
                "(58q + 12) / (30r + 28)",
                "(-18q - 84) / (30r + 28)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(-18q + 12) / (30r + 18)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtraction of two fractions results in (-18q + 12) / (30r + 18)",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "4",
            "question": "x-6/9 + 6-x/6 is simplified to which expression for all x \u2260 6?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "14/(x-6)",
                "14/(6-x)",
                "5/(x-6)",
                "5/(6-x)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "5/(x-6)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtracting the two terms results in 5/(x-6)",
            "difficulty": 4
        },
        {
            "id": "5",
            "question": "x^3/(x-3) + 6/(3-x) is simplified to which expression for all x \u2260 3?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "x+3",
                "x-3",
                "(x^3-6)/(3-x)",
                "(x^3+6)/(x-3)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(x^3-6)/(3-x)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Simplification of expression results in (x^3-6)/(3-x)",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "6",
            "question": "What is equivalent to 5y/12b - 4y/8b for b \u2260 0 ?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "y/(48b)",
                "-y/(48b)",
                "6y/(48b)",
                "-6y/(48b)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "y/(48b)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtracting the two fractions results in y/(48b).",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "7",
            "question": "7/(20r) + r/20. Which expression is equivalent to the above sum for r \u2260 0 ?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "(r^2+7)/20",
                "(r^2+7)/40",
                "(r^2-7)/20",
                "20r"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(r^2+7)/20",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Adding the two terms results in (r^2+7)/20",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "8",
            "question": "(12d/36n+33 - 6d+15/9n+14), Which expression is equivalent to the above difference?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "(12d^2 - 33d + 15) / (36n + 21)",
                "(-21d + 15) / (36n + 21)",
                "(78d + 15) / (36n + 33)",
                "(-21d - 99) / (36n + 33)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(-21d + 15) / (36n + 21)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtraction of two fractions results in (-21d + 15) / (36n + 21)",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "9",
            "question": "q-8/12 + 8-q/9 is simplified to which expression for all q \u2260 8?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "17/(q-8)",
                "17/(8-q)",
                "7/(q-8)",
                "7/(8-q)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "7/(q-8)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtraction of the two terms results in 7/(q-8)",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "10",
            "question": "q^4/(q-4) + 8/(4-q) is simplified to which expression for all q \u2260 4?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "q+4",
                "q-4",
                "(q^4-8)/(4-q)",
                "(q^4+8)/(q-4)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "(q^4-8)/(4-q)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Simplification of expression results in (q^4-8)/(4-q)",
            "difficulty": 5
        },
        {
            "id": "11",
            "question": "6m/(4a) - 8m/(7a). Which of the following expressions is equivalent to the expression above for a \u2260 0?",
            "type": "multiple_choice",
            "options": [
                "m/(28a)",
                "-m/(28a)",
                "5m/(28a)",
                "-5m/(28a)"
            ],
            "correct_answer": "m/(28a)",
            "whyCorrectAnswer": "Subtracting the two fractions results in m/(28a).",
            "difficulty": 4
        }
    ]
}